<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Keenan Cole on Keenan Cole</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Keenan Cole on Keenan Cole</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&amp;copy; 2018</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 20 Apr 2016 00:00:00 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>Mythos Unbound</title>
      <link>/project/mythos/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Jun 2018 12:43:11 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/project/mythos/</guid>
      <description>
&lt;div style=&#34;position: relative; padding-bottom: 56.25%; height: 0; overflow: hidden;&#34;&gt;
  &lt;iframe src=&#34;//www.youtube.com/embed/m0_JKJ3cFzU&#34; style=&#34;position: absolute; top: 0; left: 0; width: 100%; height: 100%; border:0;&#34; allowfullscreen title=&#34;YouTube Video&#34;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;


&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Synopsis&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/br&gt;
Mythos Unbound is an educational game designed to Greek and roman mythology in a full semester online course. Students play as a new Roman slave who must become literate in Roman culture in order to obtain their freedom. As students are taught about mythology, they enter into various levels designed to emphasize a particular characteristic of that myth. The myths include the Theogony, Odyssey, Alcestis,  Bacchae, the Oresteia and the Metamorphoses.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;/br&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Development&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/br&gt;
I developed the first and third person controller for all the levels, and designed a cooking game. I also further developed the character controllers and designed the levels for Calypso’s Island and Alcestis (Hercule’s going into the underworld).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;/img/mythos/Odyssey1.png&#34; alt=&#34;image alt text&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Saeculum</title>
      <link>/project/saeculum/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Jun 2018 12:20:35 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/project/saeculum/</guid>
      <description>
&lt;div style=&#34;position: relative; padding-bottom: 56.25%; height: 0; overflow: hidden;&#34;&gt;
  &lt;iframe src=&#34;//www.youtube.com/embed/31Hz6GOROjk&#34; style=&#34;position: absolute; top: 0; left: 0; width: 100%; height: 100%; border:0;&#34; allowfullscreen title=&#34;YouTube Video&#34;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;


&lt;p&gt;&lt;/br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Synopsis&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/br&gt;
Saeculum is first person immersive game designed to teach ancient Roman civilization in a full semester college course.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The game depicts four different time periods of Rome&amp;rsquo;s history, and students play as one of the ancestors of the Fulvii family through these different ages. In each time period, students learn about various issues that Rome faced at that time by exploring how the general population was affected, and talking with politicians, who were divided in their solutions for responding to the issues.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Students have the ability to choose how they will interact with these elements &amp;ndash; whether they will help, hurt, or hinder. In Arc 1, Rome is in the midst of the 2nd Punic War where Hannibal ravages the country side, and students must help Scipio Africanus to convince the senator to take the fight back to Carthage. In Arc 2, students come to aid of Tiberius Gracchus, who sees the need for drastic land reform, if new citizens and veterans are to have a stable way of life. In Arc 3, students must outsmart the devious Augustus Caesar while trapped as a Vestal Virgin, if they hope to continue the family legacy.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;/br&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Development&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/br&gt;
Working with artists and the lead software engineer, I developed the character pipeline that entailed creating 100+ characters for this ambitious game. We implemented lip syncing, gesture animations, locomotion system, and dynamic facial and eye animations as the base character system. The same system is also used in our Combat, Stealth, Debate, and Dialogue system.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;/img/saeculum/AtriumVestaeGarden.png&#34; alt=&#34;image alt text&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
