<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Projects on Keenan Cole</title>
    <link>/project/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Projects on Keenan Cole</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&amp;copy; 2018</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 13 Jun 2018 12:43:11 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/project/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Mythos Unbound</title>
      <link>/project/mythos/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Jun 2018 12:43:11 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/project/mythos/</guid>
      <description>Synopsis Mythos Unbound is an educational game designed to Greek and roman mythology in a full semester online course. Students play as a new Roman slave who must become literate in Roman culture in order to obtain their freedom. As students are taught about mythology, they enter into various levels designed to emphasize a particular characteristic of that myth. The myths include the Theogony, Odyssey, Alcestis, Bacchae, the Oresteia and the Metamorphoses.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Saeculum</title>
      <link>/project/saeculum/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Jun 2018 12:20:35 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/project/saeculum/</guid>
      <description>Synopsis  Saeculum is first person immersive game designed to teach ancient Roman civilization in a full semester college course.
The game depicts four different time periods of Rome&amp;rsquo;s history, and students play as one of the ancestors of the Fulvii family through these different ages. In each time period, students learn about various issues that Rome faced at that time by exploring how the general population was affected, and talking with politicians, who were divided in their solutions for responding to the issues.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>